anycodes.com 2019-06-26

# Privacy Policy - AnyCodes.com

### Last updated May 23rd, 2018.

This Privacy Policy explains how Anycodes.com ("Anycodes", "us", "we", and "our") collects and uses information when you interact with us. Please read the following policy carefully. If you do not agree to our practices, please do not interact with our site or you could also reach us for further action concerning cookie removal etc. via our Contact Information listed on the bottom of the page. This Policy may be amended or updated from time to time to reflect changes in our practices with respect to the Processing of your information, or changes in applicable law. We encourage you to read this Policy carefully, and to regularly check this page to review any changes we might make.

## Our Privacy Policy is organized as follows:

  1. What information do we collect and use?
  2. How do we use your information?
  3. Use of Cookies
  4. Third Party Cookies
  5. Children and Privacy
  6. What can you do to control your information?
  7. Contact US

## 1.  What information do we collect and use?

### a)  Personal Data

Anycodes.com does not require any personally identifiable information. However, if you opt to sign up for our newsletter or coupon alerts, you will be asked to provide certain personally identifiable information, such as name, email addresses and your favorite store. We will use the information you provide us to send you customized promotion newsletters or coupon alerts of your favorite store to your email box.

Through third party - Google Analytics, we will also collect information which cannot specifically identify an individual, and cannot be used to contact or locate a specific individual (such as age, gender, interests, zip code, state, devices, browser type, preferred language and other automatically collected information)

### b)  User Behavior Path Information

Or known as aggregated information, started from where and when you found our site and entered our site, associated with your User IP and your country recognized via your IP. IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web. Web servers (the computers that "serve up" Web pages) automatically identify your computer by its IP address; when you request a page from AnyCodes.com, our servers will record your IP address. And we will also trace your whole behavior path on our page, for example, where you clicked and which pages you visited in chronological sequence.

## 2.  How do we use your information?

We do not sell or share your information to any third parties out of MK InfoTech Limited. We may use information that we collect for the following purposes:

a)  Operate, maintain, and improve the services and our other products;

b)  Communicate with you about the coupons, advertisements, promotional offerings, and other content found on and off our products;

c)  Send you coupon alerts or customized newsletters;

d)  Monitor and improve marketing and promotional campaigns and efforts;

e)  Provide you with a personalized experience on and off our products, including targeted advertisements and promotions;

f)  Anonymize and aggregate information for different purposes, such as website traffic flow analysis, usage analysis, product development, market analysis, case studies, reports, insights, and marketing;

g)  Engage with you for the purposes of obtaining your views on our services by surveys on our products;

h)  Evaluate the types of coupons, products or services that may be of interest to users;

## 3.  Use of Cookies

A "cookie" is a small amount of information that a web server sends to your browser that stores information about your account, your preferences, and your use of our products. Some cookies contain serial numbers that allow us to connect your activity with our products with other information we store about you in your profile. Anycodes may set and access Anycodes cookies on your computer. The information from cookies and related technology is stored in web server logs and also in web cookies kept on your computers or mobile devices, which are then transmitted back to our services by your computers or mobile devices. These servers are operated and the cookies managed by us. Cookies allow AnyCodes.com to measure activity on the site and to improve your user experience, for example by remembering your viewing preferences. Anycodes also uses a Double-Click cookie to access non-personally identifiable information via Google Analytics, such as Demographics and Interest Reporting. Anycodes lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to AnyCodes' cookies.

## 4.  Third Party Cookies

### a)  Analytics

We may allow third parties to use tracking devices through our products to collect the same type of information for the same purposes as AnyCodes does for itself. For example, AnyCodes has relationships with third party advertising technology and analytics companies, such as Google Analytics to perform tracking and reporting functions for our products.

### b)  Affiliate Network

AnyCodes is in relation with Affiliate Networks, such as Commission Junction, LinkShare, ShareaSale, with whom we partner to provide certain offers, promotions or features available on or through our products and when you click on links provided by Affiliate Networks and buy something, we will earn a small commission from the advertiser at no additional cost to you.". When you leave our site to a merchant's site through one of the affiliate networks coupons or offers, Affiliate Networks will use cookies, pixels or other similar technologies on our products to collect and use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., hashed data, click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over, content viewed, search terms, location of the device, a cookie identifier, communication type (broadband or dial-up), and browser-related properties).

## 5.  Children and Privacy

a)  We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 without permission from a parent or guardian. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 has given us information, you can email us.

b)  We will promptly delete information associated with any account for which we obtain actual knowledge that the registered user associated with the account is not at least thirteen years old.

c)  AnyCodes.com encourages parents and guardians to spend time with their children online, and to be fully familiar with the sites visited by their children.

## 6.  What can you do to control your information?

You can directly take steps to change your preferences for newsletters and online behavioral advertising as outlined in this section. If you are an EU resident, you may have certain rights including: the right not to provide your Personal Information to us; the right of access to your Personal Information; the right to request rectification of inaccuracies; the right to request the erasure, or restriction of Processing, of your Personal Information; the right to object to the Processing of your Personal Information; the right to have your Personal Information transferred to another controller; the right to withdraw consent; and the right to lodge complaints with supervisory authorities. We may require proof of or need to verify your identity before we can give effect to these rights.

You can manage your email preferences by opening one of the emails we sent you, scroll to the bottom and click "unsubscribe" button anytime to opt out of our email database.

Currently, we do not recognize browser do-not-track signals. However, you may manage how your browser handles cookies and related technologies by adjusting its privacy and security settings. Browsers are different, so refer to instructions related to your browser to learn about cookie-related and other privacy and security settings that may be available. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your computer from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.

## 7.  Contact US

If you want to exercise your rights as pointed out in Section 6 or have any doubts concerning our Privacy Policy, you can always contact us by our email: [support@anycodes.com](mailto:support@anycodes.com)

USE OF THIS SITE SIGNIFIES YOUR CONSENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE.
